Your cart is empty
------------------

Have an account?

[Log in](https://black-blum.com/account/login) to check out faster.

Your cart
---------

Loading...

Subtotal
--------

£0.00 GBP

Tax included and shipping calculated at checkout

Update

Check out

Free shipping on orders over £50

Order by 18th December to receive in time for christmas

* SHOP
    
    SHOP

* ABOUT
    
    ABOUT

* UK | £

* SHOP
    
    * [
        
        shop all](https://black-blum.com/collections/all)
    * [
        
        water bottles](https://black-blum.com/collections/water-bottles)
    * [
        
        lunch boxes](https://black-blum.com/collections/lunch-boxes)
    * [
        
        thermoses](https://black-blum.com/collections/thermos-flasks)
    * [
        
        meal prep sets](https://black-blum.com/collections/meal-prep-sets)
    * [
        
        charcoal filtration](https://black-blum.com/collections/charcoal-filtration)
    * [
        
        travel cups](https://black-blum.com/collections/travel-cups)
    * [
        
        accessories](https://black-blum.com/collections/accessories)
    * [
        
        outlet](https://black-blum.com/collections/outlet)
    * [
        
        replacement parts](https://black-blum.com/collections/replacement-parts)
    
* ABOUT
    
    * [
        
        our brand](https://black-blum.com/pages/about)
    * [
        
        our sustainability](https://black-blum.com/pages/sustainability)
    * [
        
        our materials](https://black-blum.com/pages/our-materials)
    * [
        
        our blog](https://blog.black-blum.com/)
    * [
        
        contact](https://black-blum.com/pages/contactus)

Search

 Search [Log in](https://black-blum.com/account/login) [Cart

Cart](https://black-blum.com/cart)

* UK | £

T&C / Privacy Policy
====================

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

**OVERVIEW**

This website is operated by Black and Blum Ltd. Throughout the site, the terms “we”, “us”, “our”, “Black & Blum” and “black+blum” refer to:

Black and Blum Ltd, 40 Rushworth Street, London SE1 0RB, United Kingdom. Company registration number 0361 0810.

Tel +44 (0) 207 633 0022 from Europe, toll free 877 360 9222 from the USA or email [askme@black-blum.com](mailto:askme@black-blum.com)

black+blum offers this website, including all information, products and services available from this site to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies and notices stated here.

By visiting our site and/or purchasing something from us, you agree to be bound by the following Terms and Conditions, including those additional Terms and Conditions and policies referenced herein and/or available by hyperlink.

**SECTION 1 - CHANGES TO TERMS OF SERVICE**

You can review the most current version of the Terms of Service at any time on this page.

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to update, change or replace any part of these Terms of Service by posting updates and changes to our website. It is your responsibility to check our website periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to our website following the posting of any changes to these Terms of Service constitutes acceptance of those changes.

**SECTION 2 – PRICING POLICY**  
Prices and offers are subject to change without prior notice, however the products bought on the website will reflect the prices displayed at the moment of purchase withholding their unavailability at that time.

**SECTION 3 – ORDER LIMITATIONS**

We reserve the right to reject any order placed on this website and/or to limit quantities on any order without giving any reason. If we reject your order, we will always attempt to notify you using the e-mail address provided with the order. Your credit or debit card will be immediately refunded if we reject an order.

**SECTION 4 – AVAILABILITY**

Our products on sale and prices are valid as long as they are visible on the website, within the limits of stock availability. In the event of unavailability after ordering, we will inform you immediately by email or telephone. Your order will be cancelled and refunded automatically if we are unable to contact you.

**SECTION 5 – PROMOTIONAL CODES & GIFT CARDS**

Promotional codes & gift cards are debited at the time your order. Digital coupons are automatically redeemed if applicable to your purchase. Coupons cannot be replaced if they are lost, stolen, deleted, or if you cancel or return your purchase. Refunds will not be issued if the value of the coupon exceeds the value of your purchase. 

**SECTION 6 – CANCELLATION AND RETURN POLICY**

All sales are subject to black+blum’s cancellation and return policy. For the full cancellation and return as well as warranty policy, please review the refund or return and warranty sections of the website.

**SECTION 7 - SHIPPING**

**Shipping address**

The goods are delivered at the postal address provided when ordering on our website. The customer is solely responsible for the accuracy of the postal address communicated. Please review your order confirmation carefully and notify us immediately if the address needs to be amended.

When the shipping address is invalid and making delivery impossible, we will cancel the order and try and contact you by email or telephone. The payment will be refunded if we are unable to contact the customer within **5 days**. black+blum will invite the customer to re-order after verifying the delivery address.

**Lead-time**

Our warehouses dispatch orders on average within 1-4 working days. Exceptional warehouse closure periods will be indicated on the site main page or during the check out process

**Rates & delivery time estimates**

Shipping rates are calculated with the cart's amount and the delivery destination. A shipping rates calculator is available at the bottom of your shopping basket. If your country does not appear in the calculator, unfortunately we do not yet ship to your country. Please visit our Trade page for a list of distributors available in your area or contact us.

The delivery times indicated are estimated, on average delivery times. Please allow additional time during busier period such as before Christmas and your destination countries bank holidays.

black+blum reserves the right to split up the shipping of any order. black+blum cannot be held responsible for the consequences of delayed delivery.   
  
**Shipping problems**

Do not accept a package showing major damage. If accepting a damaged parcel, the customer must note any visible damage on the packaging of the goods on the delivery receipt before signing. Please take photographic evidence and notify us with a copy of the signed receipt if the goods are damaged.

Any package deposited in your mailbox or approved by someone else than you will be considered “approved” and no action can be undertaken in case of damaged goods without photographic evidence. If no claim has been issued within 3 days after the receipt of the package, we will not be able to consider potential disparities or accord any compensation.

In the rare event that your order never arrives, notification of lost items must be **received within 30 days** of the shipping confirmation e-mail.

**SECTION 8 - ERRORS, INACCURACIES AND OMISSIONS**

Prices and availability of products and services are subject to change without prior notice. Errors will be corrected where discovered, and black+blum reserves the right to revoke any stated offer and to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions including after an order has been submitted and whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is cancelled, black+blum will issue a refund to your credit card account for the amount charged. Individual bank policies will dictate when this amount is credited to your account.

**SECTION 9 – DISCLAIMERS AND LIABILITY LIMITATION**

Neither black+blum nor its parent company, affiliates, subsidiaries, designees nor each of their respective officers, directors, employees, agents, third-party content providers, designers, contractors, distributors, merchants, licensors warrant that use of this website will be uninterrupted or error-free. Neither does black+blum warrant the accuracy, integrity or completeness of the content provided on this website, nor the products and services offered for sale on this website.

black+blum specifically disclaims all warranties, whether expressed or implied, including but not limited to warranties of title, merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. No oral advice or written information given by black+blum shall create a warranty.

**SECTION 10 - CONTACT INFORMATION**

Questions about the Terms of Service should be sent to us at askme@black-blum.com.

or call +44 (0) 207 633 0022 from Europe or 877 360 9222 toll free from the USA

**SECTION 11 - AGE OF CONSENT**

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your country, state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your country, state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

**SECTION 12 – INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY**

You acknowledge and agree that all copyright, trademarks and all other intellectual property rights in all material or content supplied as part of the Website shall remain at all times the property of black+blum. You are permitted to use this material only as expressly authorised by us. You acknowledge and agree that the material and content contained within the website is made available for your personal non-commercial use only. Any other use of material and content of the website is strictly prohibited. You agree not to (and agree not to assist or facilitate and third party to) copy, reproduce, transmit, publish, display, distribute, commercially exploit or create derivative works of such material and content.

**SECTION 13 - PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Your submission of personal information through the store is governed by our Privacy Policy. Please read our Privacy Policy accessible from the footer of the website for further details.

**SECTION 14 - THIRD-PARTY LINKS**

Certain content, products and services available via our service may include materials from third-parties.

Third-party links on this site may direct you to third-party websites that are not affiliated with us. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating the content or accuracy and we do not warrant and will not have any liability or responsibility for any third-party materials or websites, or for any other materials, products, or services of third-parties.

We are not liable for any harm or damages related to the purchase or use of goods, services, resources, content, or any other transactions made in connection with any third-party websites. Please review carefully the third-party's policies and practices and make sure you understand them before you engage in any transaction. Complaints, claims, concerns, or questions regarding third-party products should be directed to the third-party.

**SECTION 15 - GOVERNING LAW**

These Terms of Service and any separate agreements whereby we provide you Services shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England.

\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

**SECTION 1 – DATA**

**WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECT?**

All personal data collected by our site is stored securely in accordance with the principles laid out by law. This data includes but is not limited to name, company name, contacting information, automatically collected IP address, web browser type and version, operating system; a list of URLs starting with a referring site and your activity on Our Site.

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?**

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR DATA?**

All personal data is stored securely in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998.

With your permission and/or where permitted by law, we may also use your data for marketing purposes which may include contacting you by email with information and industry news, and for digital advertising purposes on Google, Facebook and other third party sites. We will not send you any spam and will take all reasonable steps to ensure that We fully protect your rights and comply with Our obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, as amended in 2004, 2011 and 2015.

**SECTION 2 - CONSENT**

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at askme@black-blum.com or in writing to

Black and Blum Ltd, 40 Rushworth Street, London SE1 0RB, UK

**SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE**

We do not share customers’ details with third party websites or companies. We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms and Conditions of Sales.

**SECTION 4 - SHOPIFY**

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

Payment:

Shopify stores your credit card data encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After the completion, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

**SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**SECTION 6 – SECURITY AND THIRD-PARTY DATA**

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional, generally accepted industry standards.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable electronic and physical procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. By signing up for newsletter or submitting enquiries and selecting the checkbox, one consents to their submitted data being collected and stored for these purposes, but possible to remove their info as suited.

We use four third parties to process personal data on our behalf. These third parties have been carefully chosen and all of them comply with the current legislation. These third parties are EU-U.S. Privacy Shield compliant.

1. Google for analytics and remarketing - https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-GB
2. https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-GB for mailing list subscription and removal
3. Facebook for remarketing https://www.facebook.com/policy.
4. Omnisend for email marketing - https://www.omnisend.com/privacy/

We will also report any unlawful data breach of this website’s database or the database(s) of any of our third party data processors to any and all relevant persons and authorities within 72 hours of the breach if it is apparent that personal data stored in an identifiable manner has been stolen.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

Our website contains links to enable you to easily visit other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. The Company advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.

**SECTION 7 - COOKIES**

We use Google Analytics (GA) to track website user interaction. We use this data to determine the number of people using our site, to better understand how they find and use our web pages and to see their journey through the website.

Although GA records user data such as your geographical location, device, internet browser and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. GA also records your computer’s IP address, but Google does not grant us access to this. GA makes use of cookies, details of which can be found on Google’s developer guides. We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise trigger across the Internet. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the TriggerApp website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. The cookie is used to say, “This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page.” Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

We also use the Facebook pixel to determine people who have visited our site and use this for remarketing purposes. Facebook Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

Disabling cookies on your internet browser will stop GA and Facebook from tracking any part of your visit to pages within this website.

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

\_session\_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

\_shopify\_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits

\_shopify\_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

\_cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

\_secure\_session\_id, unique token, sessional

\_storefront\_digest, unique token, indefinite if the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

**SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

**QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you would like to access, correct, amend, delete or more information about any personal information we have about you, contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at askme@black-blum.com or in writing to:

Black+Blum, \[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer\], 40 Rushworth Street, London SE1 0RB, UK

**PROMOTIONAL TERMS & CONDITIONS**

**Free Gift With Purchase Promotion 2024:**

This promotion is active from 2nd December 2024 - 22nd December 2024. Excludes personalised products. Cannot be combined with product bundles or other discounts and promotions. Whilst stocks last. 

Learn More
----------

Help
----

Follow Us
---------

Payment methods

* PayPal
* Visa
* Mastercard
* American Express
* Klarna

© 2024, [Black+Blum UK](https://black-blum.com/)

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.
